(Penny:)Not a lot of people know this,
but the monoamine oxidase enzyme
(Penny:)was discovered by a woman,
Mary Bernheim.
(Penny:)That's right. My phone is
just as smart as you guys.
(Sheldon(off):)Amy, Bernadette, Penny.
(Bernadette:)He's never gonna stop doing that,
is he?
(Amy:)I don't mind. I'm hoping to put
his love of repetition
(Amy:)to good use someday.
(Sheldon:)Um, I've reconsidered.
(Sheldon:)You can't work where I work.
(Sheldon:)-Enjoy the rest of your evening.
-Sheldon.
(Amy:)I already signed the contract.
I cashed a check.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)You are not going
to come out of this looking good.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I don't understand.
I thought you were fine with it.
(Sheldon:)Well, I was. But that was before
Howard explained to me
(Sheldon:)how awful it would be if he had
to work with his significant other.
(Bernadette:)He said what?
(Sheldon:)Now, don't be insulted.
(Sheldon:)He just thinks too much of you would
be mind-numbingly tedious.